fusednetwork.com 2010-12-31

# Fused | Privacy Policy

Modern information and communication technologies play a fundamental role in the activities of an organization like Fused Network. We are based in Canada. Our principal activity is web hosting. 

Our privacy policy covers Fused Network and its Web site: 

Organization Name: 

| 

Fused Network   
  
---|---  
  
Address: 

| 

1170 Bay Street   
  
City, Postal Code: 

| 

Toronto, M5S2B4   
  
State: 

| 

Ontario   
  
Country: 

| 

Canada   
  
Controller: 

| 

David McKendrick   
  
Web Sites(s): 

| 

http://www.fusednetwork.com   
  
****Policy subject to change  
******The policy contained in this document may be updated, modified, or otherwise changed with notice given to you other than this document being updated.**

****Providing Visitors with Anonymous Access  
**** You can access our Web site home page and browse our site without disclosing your personal data. 

****The services and links of our Web site  
**** Our Web site enables you to communicate with other visitors or to post information to be accessed by others. When you do so, other visitors may collect your data. 

Our Web site does not include links to third party web service providers. 

**Automatic Collection of Information  
** We do not automatically log personal data nor do we link information automatically logged by other means with personal data about specific individuals. 

We use cookies to store personal data or we link information stored in cookies with personal data about specific individuals. We do so for the following purposes: 

  * Technical administration of the Web site 

**Data Collection and Purpose Specification**

We collect the personal data that you may volunteer while using our services. 

We do not collect information about our visitors from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organizations. 

We do not collect or use personal data for any purpose other than that indicated in the table below. 

If we wish to use your personal data for a new purpose, we offer you the means to consent to this new purpose: We would get in touch with the visitor if we ever needed to use their data for any other purposes beyond the ones outlined in this privacy policy. 

**Children's Privacy  
** We do not knowingly collect personal data from children. 

We take specific steps to protect the privacy of children by: 

  * making reasonable efforts to ensure that a parent has authorized the collection of the child's personal data 

We do not provide information about our personal data practices in relation to children on our home page, or at those sites on our web site where we collect personal data. 

**Disclosure and Visitor Choice  
** We do not disclose your personal data to our subsidiaries or other organizations. 

**Confidentiality / Security  
** We give you the option of using a secure transmission method to send us the following types of personal data: 

  * primary personal data (such as name and contact details) 

  * identifiers (such as credit card details, Web site password) 

We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from: 

  * unauthorized access 

  * improper use or disclosure 

  * unauthorized modification 

  * unlawful destruction or accidental loss 

All our employees and data processors, who have access to, and are associated with the processing of personal data, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of our visitors' personal data. 

We ensure that your personal data will not be disclosed to State institutions and authorities except if required by law or other regulation. 

**Access to the personal data we may hold about you  
** You can ask us, by: 

  * sending an email ( support@fusednetwork.com ) 

whether we are keeping personal data about you. 

Upon request, which you can indicate by: 

  * sending an email ( support@fusednetwork.com ) 

We will provide you with a readable copy of the personal data which we keep about you, within a week. - although we may before require proof of your identity -. We will provide the information without any charge. 

We allow you to challenge the data that we hold about you and, where appropriate, you may have the data: 

  * erased 

  * rectified or amended 

  * completed 

We reserve the right to refuse to provide our visitors with a copy of their personal data, but will give reasons for our refusal. 

We do, however, allow you to challenge our decision to refuse to provide you with a copy of your personal data. 

**Privacy Compliance  
** There are no national laws or self-regulatory schemes applicable to our web site or organization. 

There are no global or regional regulatory or self-regulatory schemes applicable to our web site or organization. 

We cannot demonstrate that our privacy policy accords with any privacy instrument provided by law. 

**Privacy Support  
** If you have an inquiry or concern about our privacy policy, please contact: 

|   
---|---  
  
Name/designation : 

| 

David McKendrick   
  
Department : 

| 

Administration   
  
Address : 

| 

1170 Bay Street  
Toronto ON M5S 2B4   
CANADA  
  
Phone Number : 

| 

1-888-282-0003   
  
Email address : 

| 

support@fusednetwork.com   
  
URL : 

| 

http://www.fusednetwork.com   
  
We do not recommend another means by which visitors' concerns may be addressed. 

TABLE of personal data collected and purposes for which they are used 

#### Primary personal data/Business information 

**x**

| 

volunteered by each visitor   
  
---|---  
  
\- 

| 

collected from public records or bodies   
  
\- 

| 

collected from private organisations
